WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
Hey... don't you want to see it?
It's about time.
What?
You know what I'm talking about.
Kakashi-sensei's... real face!
What are you doing?!
That's stupid!
I'm not interested.
Today's mission is over,
so I'm going home...
Yeah, I agree...
Aw jeez... It sounds like fun.
Maybe he has...
lips like cod roe?
Lips like cod roe, lips like cod roe,
lips like cod roe, lips like cod roe,
lips like cod roe...
Take one more push!
Or maybe buckteeth?!
Buckteeth?!
Buckteeth?! Buckteeth?!
I Want
To See,
To Know,
I Want
To Check,
Kakashi-sensei's
Real Face
But this is rare...
Here you go! Thanks for waiting!
All three of you treating me...
Snow might fall...
— Great success!
You know what I mean?
Here! Thanks for waiting!
All three of you treating me...
Snow might fall today?
Or if it's not that...
— Great success!
Maybe it's that...
Here! Thanks for waiting!
All three of you treating me...
Snow might fall today?
Or if it's not that...
are you guys up to something...
or not?
— Great success!
...like that.
Or if it's not that,
are you guys up to something?
Wh-Wh-What are you saying?!
K-Kakashi-sensei, we're celebrating
your release from the hospital!
N-Now! P-P-Please eat, eat!
All right...
Then I'll eat it without hesitation.
Thank you for waiting.
The pork slices are our treat.
Thanks for the treat.
Oh! Sasuke-kun...
What a coincidence!
Get away! Ino Pig!
Wha...?!
Aw man! I can't see at all!
I'm finished! That was good...
— So fast!
Huh? Something wrong?
N-Nothing's wrong.
Hey!
— Huh?
— Wow! I'm really curious!
Now, I will not allow myself
to be denied a glimpse of him!
But how are you
going to see it?
That's...
We'll see it somehow...
I'm asking you how! You idiot!
Then, then, do you have
a good plan, Sakura-chan?
That's...
We'll follow by completely marking him.
If we do that, he'll eventually
take his mask off.
Sasuke-kun, you are really bright.
What's that big deal?
That was so average!
Did you say something?
Well, that's fine.
What's Kakashi-sensei doing?
I'm disappointed in him.
He noticed us!
Stupid Naruto!
We were found because of you!
I tell you it's not my fault!
What?!
I-It's being made into a movie?!
I'm going to go buy
an advance ticket.
Hey, he's begun to move!
We'll follow his track!
Yeah!
What? He's gone!
Damn, he got away...
Damn it, where did he go...?
What are you guys doing?
Do you guys have
some business with me?
— N-Not really...
Hey, how did he find us out?
Isn't it because there
are too many of us?
If the presence is erased,
the number of people shouldn't matter!
Or... have you forgotten the Jutsu?
Sakura-ch-
That's you!
It will be good training to shadow him.
From now on,
we'll go about it individually.
Y-Yeah, let's just leave Naruto here!
What?!
And Junko then says...
"Oh, I am losing you."
What? What?
He got away...
Clumsy as usual...
You idiot...
Sorry.
Gosh, what is Kakashi-sensei doing?
He hasn't moved for
such a long time...
No way!
Sasuke-kun! How did it go?!
No more shadowing.
Off we go!
Today's mission is to help at a farm.
The mission itself is not a big deal.
We're definitely going to look at it...
— Kakashi-sensei's real face!
What's the matter?
You guys seem to have
lots of energy today.
— I have lots of energy!
— I'm ready to go!
Oh, that's excellent.
I've finally found you...
Hatake Kakashi!
Kakashi...
It has been a long while,
but I will settle
my long-standing grudge!
Boss, what is your grudge?
Fool! Have you forgotten?!
I cannot forget.
It happened in the spring
of three years ago...
No!
You don't need to be that scared.
Our boss says he has something
to talk to you about...
Your boss?!
I love you... Please marry me!
— Boss is so cool!
No...
There's no need to be embarrassed.
You can be honest and
fly into my arms.
No...
Don't worry.
Even though I look like this,
I have a tidy sum of money!
I am telling you, no!
What? You're turning me down
in these surroundings?
When I say no, I mean no!
I made it such a romantic setting,
but why?
I don't like what I don't like!
Why don't you stop it around there?
— Huh?
Hey, the girl doesn't like it
and no matter how you look at it,
you're being rejected, buddy.
Yeah, yeah.
You're pretty gutsy.
Do you understand who we are?!
Are you challenging us, knowing that
we are the Moya Ninja Threesome...
fearsome enough to silence
a crying child?!
Moya Ninja? Never heard of it.
You don't know Moya Ninja?!
How dare you make fools of us!
Who the hell are you?
It's not worth enough to introduce, but...
Well, my name is Hatake Kakashi.
— You're introducing yourself!
Hey you...
You're going to regret it.
For getting in the way of
someone's romance!
Romance?
Isn't it just an annoying,
one-sided love?
Enough!
Men! We're going to attack!
— Yes, sir!
4... 3... 2... 1...
— Hustle! Hustle!
Please! Somebody help me!
Hey! I can't stand heights!
I'll take you back to the village.
Stop talking! Hey!
Hey, quit sighing!
What, are you just leaving us here?!
That's how it went...
— Don't be so proud!
— You lost!
So it means revenge from
three years ago!
Boss has become stronger
in the last three years,
and he's going to beat him up
in a face-to-face match!
That's so dramatic!
Fool! Who would take such risk?!
Huh?
If we're going to do it,
we'll do it stealthily from
the shadows! Stealthily.
— D-Dirty!
Welcome!
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
Incredible!
Looks delicious!
How extravagant.
Please take your time...
Kakashi...
Now eat, this will be
your last dinner party.
That meal contains
a tasteless and odorless medicine
that causes uncontrollable hiccups.
Just keep on having
the ceaseless hiccups and die suffering!
It's a fitting end for you!
Something wrong?
Not one of you has
even laid chopsticks on the food.
Not really, but why don't you,
Kakashi-sensei, hurry up and eat?
Well, I'm on a diet.
Figured he'd say something like that.
Then I'll strip off that mask
if it kills me!
My hands slipped...
How could you!
Oh, sorry, sorry, I unintentionally...
— What do you mean "unintentionally"?!
What a pity! The meal...
— How could he do such a thing?!
Hey, what's the next move?
Don't worry. I have an idea.
— An idea?
I see, this is pretty good thinking
for Sasuke.
A person would normally
take off the mask here.
Never mind that.
Just be quiet, you idiot!
Kakashi, you will die here!
From this needle on the blowpipe arrow,
coated with medicine I prepared
that will make you laugh uncontrollably...
You'll die laughing...
That is the fitting way for you...
Damn...
I wanted to see it too,
but this is a hot spring...
But I want to see!
Kakashi-sensei!
Aren't you ready yet?
All right, I'm coming in now.
I do want to see it!
— Here he comes!
— Great!
Oh, I can't see at all!
Thanks for waiting.
I'll just soak for a little while.
— Why is it like this?!
Now!
Huh? Something wrong?
And slowly, I sink in.
What the...?!
What happened?
I want to know!
What in the world is
Kakashi-sensei thinking? Huh?
Damn, I'm completely flushed... Huh?
— Our clothes are gone!
Please come again!
Thank you for coming!
Crap... I'm going to
definitely defeat you, Hatake Kakashi.
But it was great that
we brought spare clothes.
I wonder who took them away...?
Our clothes!
All right,
each of you work at your own posts.
Now, break up.
I can't stand it anymore...
I have too much stress stored inside.
I'm almost at the end of
my patience as well...
Sasuke-kun... actually, me too...
Then, it's the last resort!
— Last resort?
What is this?
Can't you see? It's a Shinobi outfit.
When did you get this ready?
Well, well, never mind that,
never mind that.
What do you do with this?
We'll strip away the mask.
Even if we have to use force!
Damn Kakashi...
Boss! Look at that!
Hey, Hatake Kakashi!
Hey, what are you guys up to?
W-What are you talking about?
We are simply Ninja.
It is not that we want to see
what is behind your mask...!
Fool! Don't say unnecessary things!
That's...!
Boss! There's somebody else besides you
who holds a grudge on Kakashi!
Now is the chance!
Right! Let's go!
— Right!
Stop right there!
Kakashi! It's time for you
to pay for your crime!
You shall die!
With this medicine I prepared
that will make you cry... What?!
Oh, just when I thought how long
you guys were going to sneak around...
you finally come out.
Ah, well, you know...
But before that,
Sasuke, Sakura, Naruto!
Why are you guys dressed like that?
Huh?! Well, yeah, so...
Oh no...
We have to make up an explanation,
whatever it is!
Caught you!
We were well aware that
you three were targeting Kakashi-sensei!
What?! Then our plot was exposed
from the beginning!
Of course!
This was a trap to lure you guys out!
We caught you off guard!
So we were completely caught
in the trap.
Damn! We underestimated you,
thinking it was kids!
I never heard that story!
Nice, Sakura!
I don't quite get what's happening,
but oh well...
— Please forgive us!
There's no use talking...
— O-Oh no!
— S-Stop!
It's the same as three years ago!
This time, we're hung by just one rope,
combined with the same movement.
By the way, who are you guys?
— And he doesn't even remember us!
Hey, Kakashi-sensei.
Yeah?
What is behind that mask?
What? You wanted to see
what's behind this mask?
Yeah!
Then you should have said
that from the beginning...
Well, can you show us?
I don't mind...
What the...?!
Sure thing.
All right...
Is it like cod roe?
Buckteeth?
Or a tiny mouth?
Behind this mask...
— Behind that mask...
There happens to be another mask!
— What?!
What...?!
What in the world is that?!
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
Begging your pardon!
I was born and raised in the Leaf Village
in the Land of Fire.
My given name is Naruto,
and the surname is Uzumaki.
People call me...
"The No. 1 Hyperactive
Knucklehead Ninja"!
I'm not "the No. 1 Hyperactive"
What's this
you've been practicing?
We're going to meet with
Boss Wasabi.
A proper first greeting's important!
Next time:
"Come Now, New Mission. Save the Obligation, The Sympathy and the Country of Tea!"